<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Abacus Shapes</title>
    <link>https://abacusgame.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Abacus Shapes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ja-JP</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 21:30:07 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://abacusgame.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Clone_technology</title>
      <link>https://abacusgame.github.io/blog/clone_technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 21:30:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abacusgame.github.io/blog/clone_technology/</guid>
      <description>Current medical technology can make clones of creatures. The clone becomes an Identical twin of the original one. We can ask a surrogate mather to give birth to a clone baby. Plants or single cell creatures propagate themselves with clones. Graft technology is possible with plants. There are Siamese twins. If an old man make a clone of him and graft it on him, then they will be Siamese twins. Or if we embed the clone into the the old man&amp;rsquo;s body like a pregnant woman, it will grow inside of his body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corona_virus</title>
      <link>https://abacusgame.github.io/blog/corona_virus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 21:30:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abacusgame.github.io/blog/corona_virus/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve finally got a vaccination against corona virus.
The effect was heavy. What I realized after getting the vaccination was
that I&amp;rsquo;ve just underestimated the virus. During this pandemic, I went to
public places many times wearing masks. I thought that I was sturdy enough
to repel the virus. But after getting the vaccination, I had suffered from terrible symptoms of the vaccine. I felt killing chill. I spent night gasping all night sweating soggy in my bed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drone_technology</title>
      <link>https://abacusgame.github.io/blog/drone_technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 21:30:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abacusgame.github.io/blog/drone_technology/</guid>
      <description>Drone
One of my dreams is to fly in the sky freely. Now drone is getting popular these days.
They use VR camera to watch the scene from the drone. Instead of VR camera,
I&amp;rsquo;d like to propose a way to use 360 degrees camera. Not only one screen ahead, but also cameras on both sides, up and down, and behind your body. Then you will feel like you&amp;rsquo;re really sitting in a cockpit of the drone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food_delivery</title>
      <link>https://abacusgame.github.io/blog/food_delivery/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 21:30:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abacusgame.github.io/blog/food_delivery/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve worked as a delivery worker of Uber Eats and Demaekan. I bought a bag below. When I bought it, it costs 4000 yen. But now the price is increased. But perhaps you can find a web site that sells it with 4000 yen. The bag was useful but heavy. It can hold PET bottle to drink water with a net beside it. It was a good point, but to tell the truth, I didn&amp;rsquo;t use this bag to put foods in it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Progressive_supranuclear_palsy</title>
      <link>https://abacusgame.github.io/blog/progressive_supranuclear_palsy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 21:30:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abacusgame.github.io/blog/progressive_supranuclear_palsy/</guid>
      <description>My dad is suffeing from a disease called progressive supranuclear palsy: PSP. Nowadays, I&amp;rsquo;m caring my parent everyday. Caring disabled is hassle. He is very heavy to support. He can&amp;rsquo;t keep his balance. I need to control his balance when I try to make him walk. He is almost bedridden. But I think that walking with his own foot is quite important. To keep standing while feeling vertical stimulation of gravity strengthen bones and stimulate the secretion of some proper hormon, I guess.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traffic_technology</title>
      <link>https://abacusgame.github.io/blog/traffic_technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 21:30:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abacusgame.github.io/blog/traffic_technology/</guid>
      <description>Fail safe traffic system.
It&amp;rsquo;s technically not difficult to make such system with the current technology.
I wonder why people won&amp;rsquo;t make it immediately.
People are facing aging society. Elderly people are prone to make mistakes while
they are driving. So the possibility to see such tragedies won&amp;rsquo;t be reduced
if we don&amp;rsquo;t do anything.
Install communication devices into every vehicles like number plates
or regular automobile inspection. Install passive controller of speed and steering into all vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
